Guide to the Jerome New Frank Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE & SUBJECTS FILE 1933-1937, Circa May 1933-Circa November 1937; Series II; 5' (12 boxes)
  - Correspondence
    - Frankfurter, Felix., 1933-1936 (Box 12, Folder 84)
      See also: David E. Lilienthal and Melville F. Weston
    - Freund, Paul, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 85)
    - Friant, Julien N., 1934 (Box 12, Folder 86)
    - Fuller, Leonore B., 1934 (Box 12, Folder 87)
      See also: box 12, folder 86
    - G, 1933-1936 (Box 12, Folder 88)
    - Gannett, Lewis (Box 12, Folder 89)
    - Garrison, Lloyd K., 1934 (Box 12, Folder 90)
    - Glueck, Bernard, 1933-1935 (Box 12, Folder 91)
    - Gourrich, Paul P., 1933-1934 (Box 12, Folder 92)
    - Green, Leon, 1933, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 93)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 8/4
    - Gruening, Ernest, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 94)
    - Gunther, John and Frances, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 95)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 3-1/0
    - H, 1933-1937 (Box 12, Folder 96)
    - Hamilton, Walton H., 1933-1934 (Box 12, Folder 97)
    - Handler, Milton, 1933, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 98)
    - Harvard Law Review, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 99)
    - Hayes, Ralph, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 100)
    - Helburn, Willard, 1933-1935 (Box 12, Folder 101)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 13/4
    - Henderson, Leon, undated (Box 12, Folder 102)
    - Herzberg, Ben, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 103)
    - Hewes, Thomas, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 104)
    - Hicks, Frederick C., 1933-1934 (Box 12, Folder 105)
    - Hiss, Alger., 1934-1935 (Box 12, Folder 106)
      See also: box 10, folder 61 See also: box 11, folder 62 See also: box 13, folder 142 See also: box 182, Folder 44
    - Holly, William H., 1933, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 107)
    - Hopkins, Harry, 1933-1935 (Box 12, Folder 108)
    - Howe, Frederic C., 1933-1934 (Box 12, Folder 109)
      See also: box 30, folder 339
    - Hunt, Henry T. and Eleanor (Phelps), 1933-1934 (Box 12, Folder 110)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 6-2/2
    - I, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 111)
    - Ickes, Harold L., 1934 (Box 12, Folder 112)
    - Illinois Law Review, 1933, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 113)
    - J, 1933, 1935-1936 (Box 12, Folder 114)
    - Jackson, Gardner, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 115)
    - Jackson, Percival E., 1933-1935 (Box 12, Folder 116)
    - Jackson, Robert, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 117)
    - Javits, Benjamin A., 1934 (Box 12, Folder 118)
    - Johnson, Alvin, 1933-1934 (Box 12, Folder 119)
    - Johnson, Hugh S., 1934 (Box 12, Folder 120)
    - K, 1933-1936 (Box 12, Folder 121)
    - L, 1933-1936 (Box 12, Folder 122)
    - LaGuardia, Fiorello H., 1935 (Box 12, Folder 123)
    - Landis, James M., 1934-1935 (Box 12, Folder 124)
    - Legal education: reactions to JNF's proposed reforms., 1933-1934 (Box 12, Folder 125)
      See also: box 154, folder 408 See also: box 155, folder 417 See also: box 166, folder 592
    - Levinson, David, 1933-1934 (Box 13, Folder 126)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 12/9
    - Levinson, Salmon O., 1933-1935 (Box 13, Folder 127)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 11/4
    - Levy, Beryl Harold, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 128)
    - Levy, David M., 1934-1935 (Box 13, Folder 129)
    - Lewin, John Henry, 1933-1935 (Box 13, Folder 130)
    - Lewis, Clarence M., 1933-1934 (Box 13, Folder 131)
    - Liebman, Walter H., 1934-1935 (Box 13, Folder 132)
    - Lilienthal, David E., 1933-1934 (Box 13, Folder 133)
    - Lindsey, Ben B., 1933-1935 (Box 13, Folder 134)
    - Liquor Control Plan: proposed government monopoly memoranda, 1933 (Box 13, Folder 135)
    - Llewellyn, Karl N., 1933-1935 (Box 13, Folder 136)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 21/14
    - Lowenthal, Max, 1933-1934 (Box 13, Folder 137)
    - M, 1933-1936 (Box 13, Folder 138)
    - McCormick, Charles T., 1936 (Box 13, Folder 139)
    - Mack, Julian W., 1933-1934 (Box 13, Folder 140)
    - Macmillan Company, The, 1934-1935 (Box 13, Folder 141)
    - Marketing Agreements: AAA general policy concerning "Books and Records Clause" Jan-Mar, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 142)
    - Marketing Agreements: AAA general policy concerning "Books and Records Clause" Mar-Jun, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 143)
    - Marketing Agreements: California canned asparagus industry, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 144)
    - Marketing Agreements: California canned cling peach industry, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 145)
    - Marketing Agreements: California raisins, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 146)
    - Marketing Agreements: meat packing industry, 1933-1934 (Box 13, Folder 147-148)
    - Marketing Agreements: milk--general AAA policy, 1933 (Box 13, Folder 149)
    - Marketing Agreements: milk--licences in California. Correspondence with and about Roy M. Pike, 1933-1934 (Box 14, Folder 150)
    - Marketing Agreements: milk--licences in Chicago, 1933-1934 (Box 14, Folder 151)
    - Marketing Agreements: milk--memorandum to the Secretary of December 12 in re violations of marketing agreement for the Chicago milk shed, 1933-1934 (Box 14, Folder 152)
    - Marketing Agreements: milk--data pertaining to revocation of licences in the Chicago milk shed and abstracts from the transcript of the hearing in Chicago, Nov 27-Dec 2, 1933 (Box 14, Folder 153)
    - Marketing Agreements: milk--Philadelphia milk shed audit, 1933 (Box 14, Folder 154)
    - newspaper clippings and copies of newspaper articles from folder marked "JNF--Personal", 1933 (Box 14, Folder 155)
    - Marketing Agreements: rice industry, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 156)
    - Marketing Agreements: sugar industry, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 157)
    - Marketing Agreements: tobacco industry, 1933 (Box 14, Folder 158)
    - Maverick, Maury., 1935 (Box 14, Folder 159)
      See also: box 9, folder 14
    - May, Mark A., 1933-1934 (Box 14, Folder 160)
    - Mayer, Arthur L., 1934-1935 (Box 14, Folder 161)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 3/6
    - Means, Gardiner., 1935 (Box 14, Folder 162)
    - Michael, Jerome, 1935-1936 (Box 14, Folder 163)
    - Miller, John S., 1933-1934 (Box 14, Folder 164)
    - Moley, Raymond, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 165)
    - Morgan, E. M., 1933, 1935 (Box 14, Folder 166)
      See also: John S. Bradway
    - Morgenthau, Henry Jr., 1933 (Box 14, Folder 167)
    - Morley, Felix., 1936 (Box 14, Folder 168)
      See also: box 10, folder 24
    - Morris, George Maurice, 1933-1934 (Box 14, Folder 169)
    - Morris, James W., 1935, 1937 (Box 14, Folder 170)
    - N, 1933-1935 (Box 14, Folder 171)
    - The Nation, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 172)
    - Neblett, William H., 1934-1935 (Box 14, Folder 173)
    - Nourse, Edwin G., 1934 (Box 14, Folder 174)
    - O, 1933-1934 (Box 14, Folder 175)
    - Ogden, C. K., 1933 (Box 14, Folder 176)
    - P-Q, 1933-1936 (Box 14, Folder 177)
    - Paul, Randolph, 1933-1936 (Box 15, Folder 178)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 26/5
    - Pearson, Drew, 1934 (Box 15, Folder 179)
    - Peek, George N., 1933 (Box 15, Folder 180)
    - Pennsylvania Law Review, 1933-1934 (Box 15, Folder 181)
    - Phleger, Herman, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 182)
    - Powell, Thomas Reed, 1934 (Box 15, Folder 183)
    - Pressman, Lee, 1933-1935 (Box 15, Folder 184)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 22/6
      See also: box 16, folder 214 See also: box 11, folder 63
    - Public utilities in Wisconsin memoranda, 1934 (Box 15, Folder 185)
    - Public works: loans for home building memoranda, 1933 (Box 15, Folder 186)
    - Public Works Administration: JNF's appointment as consulting legal counsel, 1935 (Box 15, Folder 187)
    - Public Works Administration: memoranda and information concerning its formation, 1933 (Box 15, Folder 188)
    - Public Works Administration: memoranda on proposed public works bill dealing with highways, 1933 (Box 15, Folder 189)
    - Public Works Administration: memoranda on Kent and Rorty Plans (forced expansion of industry), undated (Box 15, Folder 190)
    - R, 1933-1936 (Box 15, Folder 191)
    - Railroad Reorganization: memoranda to Cassius Clay from JNF and John Howland, Apr-Jun., 1935 (Box 15, Folder 192)
      See also: box 24, folder 134
    - Railroad Reorganization: memoranda to Cassius Clay from JNF and John Howland, Jul-Oct, 1935 (Box 15, Folder 193)
    - Reed, Stanley, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 194)
    - Rich, Martha, 1935, undated (Box 15, Folder 195)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 196)
    - Ryan, Oswald, 1934-1935 (Box 15, Folder 197)
    - S, 1933-1936 (Box 15, Folder 198)
    - Schwartz, Ulysses S., 1933-1935 (Box 15, Folder 199)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 10/10
    - Schwellenbach, Lewis B., 1935 (Box 15, Folder 200)
    - Sinclair, Upton, 1935 (Box 15, Folder 201)
    - Sommerich, Otto, 1933, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 202)
    - Stedman, Alfred D., 1933-1935 (Box 15, Folder 203)
      See also: box 11, folder 62
    - Stephens, Harold M., 1933-1935 (Box 15, Folder 204)
      See also: box 16, folder 214 box 10, folder 61
    - Stern, Alfred K., 1933-1934 (Box 15, Folder 205)
      See also: box 41, folder 725 See also: box 16, folder 214
    - Stevenson, Adlai E., 1934 (Box 15, Folder 206)
      See: box 14, folder 151
    - Stolz, Leon, 1934 (Box 15, Folder 207)
    - Sturges, Wesley A., 1933-1934 (Box 15, Folder 208)
    - Sugar Act of 1937 (O'Mahoney-Adams bill) memoranda (Box 15, Folder 209)
      See also: box 20, folders 280-282
    - Swaine, Robert T., 1933 (Box 16, Folder 210)
    - Swiren, Max, 1933-1934 (Box 16, Folder 211)
    - T, 1933-1934 (Box 16, Folder 212)
    - Thomas, Seth., 1933-1934 (Box 16, Folder 213)
      See also: box 11, folder 62 box 11, folder 63
    - Tugwell, Rexford Guy, 1933-1935, 1937 (Box 16, Folder 214)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 6/28
    - U-V, 1933-1934 (Box 16, Folder 215)
    - United States government agencies, 1933-1935 (Box 16, Folder 216)
    - Viking Press, The, 1933 (Box 16, Folder 217)
    - Virginia Law Review, 1933-1935 (Box 16, Folder 218)
    - W, 1933-1935 (Box 16, Folder 219)
    - Wagner, Robert F., 1935 (Box 16, Folder 220)
    - Wallace, Henry A., 1933-1936 (Box 16, Folder 221)
    - Wenchel, J. P., 1934 (Box 16, Folder 222)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 10/3
      See also: all general AAA correspondence
    - Westervelt, W. I., 1933, 1935 (Box 16, Folder 223)
    - Williams, Aubrey, 1935 (Box 16, Folder 224)
    - Wilson, Francis S., 1934 (Box 16, Folder 225)
    - Wolff, Herbert A., 1935-1936 (Box 16, Folder 226)
    - Woodall, Emery J., 1933-1934 (Box 16, Folder 227)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 8/1
    - Woolsey, John M., 1935 (Box 16, Folder 228)
    - X-Y-Z, 1933-1934, 1936 (Box 16, Folder 229)
    - Yale Law Journal, 1933-1935 (Box 16, Folder 230)
    - Yale University, 1933-1934 (Box 16, Folder 231)
    - Yntema, Hessel E., 1933 (Box 16, Folder 232)
    - Letters of Recommendation, 1933-1935 (Box 16, Folder 233)
    - Unidentified, 1934 (Box 16, Folder 234)
    - Chronological Files
      - Personal correspondence, Apr-Jun, 1933 (Box 16, Folder 235)
      - Personal correspondence, Jul-Dec, 1933 (Box 16, Folder 236)
      - Personal correspondence, Jan-Jun, 1934 (Box 16, Folder 237)
      - Personal correspondence, Jul-Dec, 1934 (Box 16, Folder 238)
      - Personal correspondence, Jan-Apr, 1935 (Box 16, Folder 238)
      - Outgoing AAA letters and memoranda, May-Dec, 1933 (Box 16, Folder 239)
      - Outgoing AAA letters and memoranda, Jan-Feb, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 240)
      - Outgoing AAA letters and memoranda, Mar, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 241)
      - Outgoing AAA letters and memoranda, Apr, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 242)
      - Outgoing AAA letters and memoranda, May, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 243)
      - Outgoing AAA letters and memoranda, Jun, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 244)
      - Outgoing AAA letters and memoranda, Jul-Aug, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 245)
      - Outgoing AAA letters and memoranda, Sep-Oct 5, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 246)
      - Outgoing AAA letters and memoranda, Oct 6-31, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 247)
      - Outgoing AAA letters and memoranda, Nov, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 248)
      - Outgoing AAA letters and memoranda, Dec, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 249)
      - Outgoing AAA letters and memoranda, Jan 2-15, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 250)
      - Outgoing AAA letters and memoranda, Jan 16-31-Apr, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 251)
  - Subjects File
    - biographical information on Thomas S. Martin, undated (Box 18, Folder 252)
    - congressional bill to amend Title I of the National Industrial Recovery Act, undated (Box 18, Folder 253)
    - congressional bill to provide for the custody of Federal proclamations, orders, regulations, notices and other documents and for the prompt and uniform printing and distribution thereof, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 254)
    - dates when JNF was absent from AAA office and J. P. Wenchel was designated Acting General Counsel, 1933-1934 (Box 18, Folder 255)
    - Duke Power Company and Southern Public Utilities Company v. Greenwood County and E. L. Brooks, S. A.Agnew, E. T. Davis, et al., 1937 (Box 18, Folder 256)
    - excerpts from testimony of George N. Peek on Mar 24 before the Senate Committee on Agriculture and Forestry in hearings on H. R. 3835, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 257)
    - Federal Emergency Relief Administration: proposed additions to regulations, undated (Box 18, Folder 258)
    - legal briefs concerning power company cases, [1935?] (Box 18, Folder 259)
    - legal memorandum for Judge Pound concerning Aetna Casualty and Surety Co. v. Tramley,Inc.Co-authored with William O. Douglas, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 260)
    - legal memorandum: The Emergency Banking Act Joint Resolution No. 10 of Jun 5, 1933 and The Gold Reserve Act of 1934 Constitute Rules of Decision Binding upon the Court of Claims, undated (Box 18, Folder 261)
    - newspaper clippings and copies of newspaper articles on AAA through Jul, 1934 (Box 19, Folder 262)
    - newspaper clippings and copies of newspaper articles on AAA, Aug, 1934 (Box 19, Folder 263)
    - newspaper clippings and copies of newspaper articles on AAA, Sep-Jan, 1934-1935 (Box 19, Folder 264)
    - statement about Dr. William A. Wirt--a defense of the New Deal, 1933-1935 (Box 19, Folder 265)
    - newspaper clippings and copies of newspaper articles on cotton, 1933-1934 (Box 19, Folder 266)
    - newspaper clippings and copies of newspaper articles on farmers' strikes, 1933-1934 (Box 19, Folder 267)
    - newspaper clippings and copies of newspaper articles of milk marketing agreements, 1933-1934 (Box 19, Folder 268)
    - newspaper clippings and copies of newspaper articles on sugar marketing agreements, 1934 (Box 19, Folder 269)
    - notes on Justice Brandeis' views on huge corporations (unsigned), undated (Box 19, Folder 270)
    - notes on the progress of the Roth case (unsigned), undated (Box 19, Folder 271)
    - notes on The Roosevelt Revolution by Ernest K. Lindley (unsigned), undated (Box 19, Folder 272)
    - press releases; AAA--general information, 1933-1934 (Box 19, Folder 273)
    - press releases: milk marketing agreements, 1933-1934 (Box 19, Folder 274)
    - press releases: sugar marketing agreements, 1934 (Box 19, Folder 275)
    - questions and answers about the AAA (unsigned), 1934 (Box 19, Folder 276)
    - record of law review articles and speeches by Jerome Frank, 1932-1933 (Box 20, Folder 277)
    - report of a trip made by Herbert A. Wolff and Theodore S. Jaffin to Miami concerning Trimbur v. Cities Service, undated (Box 20, Folder 278)
    - resolution by the board of directors of the South Carolina Public Service Authority concerning legal services performed by JNF, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 279)
    - Sugar Act of 1937 (O'Mahoney-Adams bill): notes, reports and clippings (Box 20, Folder 280-282)
    - statement by Joseph B. Eastman, Federal Coordinator of Transportation, Oct 4, 1933 (Box 20, Folder 283)
    - statement concerning the testimony of Frederic P. Lee before a Senate committee investigating air mail service, 1934 (Box 20, Folder 284)
    - statement concerning "the recent purge in the Department of Agriculture" (unsigned), [1935?] (Box 20, Folder 285)
    - press release: WOL Press Department--Symposium on recovery program, [1934?] (Box 20, Folder 286)
    - survey of the Agricultural Adjustment Act after a year and a half of operation, 1934 (Box 20, Folder 287)
    - travel vouchers: Reconstruction Finance Corporation, 1935 (Box 20, Folder 288)
- CORRESPONDENCE & SUBJECTS FILE 1937-1941, Circa December 1937-Circa April 1941; Series III; 10' (24 boxes)
  Correspondence is arranged alphabetically by the name of the writer of the letter, by the name of an organization or by topic. Correspondence with Securities and Exchange Commission officials may be found in the topics folders as well as in the folders under their names. A list of these officials appears on the following page. Letters written by Jerome Frank are filed under the name of the person to whom the letter was addressed. The correspondence is followed by a small subjects file arranged alphabetically by topic.
  Consult the folder title listings in each of the four correspondence series for correspondence of a particular individual, organization or topic.
  The following people worked for the Securities and Exchange Commission:
  Allen, James
  Brassor, Francis P.
  Burke, Edmond
  Clark, Samuel O. Jr.
  Coolidge, Roger S.
  Davis, Sherlock
  Douglas, William O. *
  Durkin, Gladys R.
  Eicher, Edward C. *
  Fields, Morris J.
  Freedman, Walter
  Fortas, Abe
  Ginsberg, David
  Goldschmidt, R. W.
  Gourrich, Paul P.
  Guthrie, C. S.
  Hanes, John W. *
  Healy, Robert E. *
  Henderson, Leon *
  Lane, Chester T.
  Mathews, George C.*
  Meltzer, Bernard
  Nehemkis, Peter R.
  Pike, Sumner
  Purcell, Ganson
  Schenker, David
  Shaughnessy, M. Quinn
  Smith, C. Roy
  Throop, Allen E.
  Timberg, Sigmund
  Weiner, Joseph L.
  * Commissioner
  Additional SEC memoranda may be found under the following subject headings:
  Columbia Gas and Electric Corporation case
  German Bonds memoranda
  Greer, William A.: memoranda concerning his criminal activities
  Metropolitan Life Insurance Company investigation
  Monopoly Study (TNEC) memoranda
  North American Company case
  Railroad reorganization memoranda
  Smith, C. Roy: resignation from the SEC
  Stabilization: memoranda by JNF and others
  Temporary National Economic Committee memoranda
  United Corporation case
  Whitney, Richard and the New York Stock Exchange case
  - Correspondence
    - A, 1938-1941 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Abt, John J., 1939-1940 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Acheson, Dean G., 1939 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Aitchison, Clyde B., 1938-1939 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Allen, Florence E., 1940 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Allen, Frederick Lewis, 1938-1940 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Allen, James, 1938-1941 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Allen Robert S., 1938-1940 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Alsop, Joseph, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - American Bar Association, 1938-1941 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Amlie, Thomas R., undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Anderson, Arthur, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Anderson, Richard J., 1939 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Anderson, Victor E., 1938-1939 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Appleby, Paul H., 1937-1941 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 21/32
    - Armstrong, William Campbell, 1937-1941 (Box 21, Folder 16)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 11/5
    - Arnold, Thurman W., 1938-1941 (Box 21, Folder 17)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 7/16
    - Ascher, Charles S., 1938-1939, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 18)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 6/0
    - Aswell, Edward C., 1938-1939 (Box 21, Folder 19)
      See: box 29, folder 295
    - B, 1937-1941 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Bachrach, Arthur, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Backer, George, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Bailie, Earle, 1939 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Baldwin, Roger N., 1938 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Baltimore Sun editor, 1938-1940 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Bane, Frank, 1938, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Barkley, Alben W., 1940 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Barnes, John P., 1937-1938 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Barriger, J. W., 1940 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Batt, W. L., 1940 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Bauer, John, 1938-1939 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Beach, W. Edwards, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Bean, Louis H., 1938-1940 (Box 21, Folder 33)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 6/4
    - Beck, Thomas H., 1938-1939 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Becker, Benjamin V., 1938-1941 (Box 21, Folder 35)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 27/14
      See also: box 30, folder 346
    - Becker, Harry, 1939 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Bell, D. W., 1939-1940 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Berenson, Arthur, 1938 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Berger, Raoul, 1938, 1940, undated (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Bergmann, L. V., 1939 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Berle, Adolph A., 1938-1941 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Bernard, Albert, 1939 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Bernstein, Henry, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Bertrand, Daniel, 1938 (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Biddle, Francis, 1939-1941 (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Bigelow, Harry A., 1938 (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - Bingham, Alfred M., 1939-1941 (Box 22, Folder 47)
    - Bittker, Boris. I., 1941 (Box 22, Folder 48)
    - Black, Hugo L., 1940-1941 (Box 22, Folder 49)
    - Black, William Harman, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 50)
    - Blair, John M., 1939 (Box 22, Folder 51)
    - Blaisdell, Thomas C. Jr., 1938-1939, 1941, n.d (Box 22, Folder 52)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 24/3
    - Bliven, Bruce, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 53)
    - Blunt, John E., 1937-1938 (Box 22, Folder 54)
    - Bogen, Jules I., 1938, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 55)
    - Bolton-Smith, Carlile, 1938, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 56)
    - Bonbright, James C., 1939 (Box 22, Folder 57)
    - Bone, Homer T., 1939-1940 (Box 22, Folder 58)
      See also: box 28, folder 281
    - Borah, William E., 1938-1939 (Box 22, Folder 59)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 0/3
    - Bordwell, Percy, 1938 (Box 22, Folder 60)
    - Boyden, Preston, 1937-1939 (Box 22, Folder 61)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 5/1
    - Brackett, James R., 1938, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 62)
    - Brady, John F., 1938 (Box 22, Folder 63)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 7/0
    - Brandeis, Louis D., 1938-1941 (Box 22, Folder 64)
    - Brassor, Francis P., 1938-1941 (Box 22, Folder 65)
    - Brodnitz, Otto W., 1941 (Box 22, Folder 66)
      See also: box 32, folder 395
    - Bromley, Bruce, 1939 (Box 22, Folder 67)
    - Brougham, Herbert Bruce, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 68)
    - Brown, Lawrence, 1938 (Box 22, Folder 69)
    - Bruce, Edward, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 70)
    - Bruce, James, 1937-1938 (Box 22, Folder 71)
    - Buell, Raymond Leslie, 1938-1939 (Box 22, Folder 72)
    - Bunbury, Henry, 1938 (Box 22, Folder 73)
    - Burke, Edmond Jr., 1938, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 74)
    - Burlew, E. K., 1940 (Box 22, Folder 75)
    - Burnett, Whit, 1940-1941 (Box 22, Folder 76)
    - Burns, John J., 1938 (Box 22, Folder 77)
    - C, 1938-1941 (Box 22, Folder 78)
    - Cahill, John T., 1939 (Box 23, Folder 79)
    - Cairns, Huntington, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 80)
    - Calkins, Howard W., 1941 (Box 23, Folder 81)
    - Calverton, V. F., 1937 (Box 23, Folder 82)
    - Campbell, Marcus B., 1938 (Box 23, Folder 83)
    - Canaday, R. O., 1939 (Box 23, Folder 84)
    - Carmody, John M., 1939, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 85)
    - Carter, Boake, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 86)
    - Carusi, Eugene, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 87)
    - Case, James H. Jr., 1938 (Box 23, Folder 88)
    - Catlin, George E. G., 1940 (Box 23, Folder 89)
    - Cellar, Emanuel, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 90)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 4/5
    - Chamberlain, John, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 91)
    - Chase, Cecil, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 92)
    - Chase, Stuart, 1937-1940 (Box 23, Folder 93)
    - Cheatham, Elliott E., 1937 (Box 23, Folder 94)
    - Cheney, William L., 1938 (Box 23, Folder 95)
    - Chicago Bar Association, 1938-1939 (Box 23, Folder 96)
    - Chicago Daily News, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 97)
      See: box 34, folder 505
    - Chicago Tribune, 1938-1940 (Box 23, Folder 98)
      See: box 39, folder 659